A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Marie?
Everything is fine. I am calm and collected. I think I've experimented with my own body more than enough to know.
Ever since then.
No. It can't be happening yet. I still have things left to do, damn it.
I can't start losing it. I can't afford to.
I'm falling down to my shadow 息をひそめて 待っている the dream life
Don't scare me 君が望めば どんな世界も その目に映せるから
See you in your dreams, yeah, baby
怖い夢 だとしても
テレブル 君のために 星を砕ぎ 飾り付けた
Black paper
Bum, bum
信じてくれたなら
When you lost your world
Forever with your soul
見上がれば 輝く 月のように
Marie has been worried about you, you know
She says that you seem to be getting more and more exhausted lately
Maybe it's time for you to take a little vacation
Get away from it all for a while
Don't worry, there's no cause for alarm
I'm still entirely capable of teaching class
It was just a temporary muscle issue
I see
Then I'll trust you to do as you see fit
In fact, there's something specific I want you to work on
Arachnophobia has supposedly found the location of Brew
Brew, huh?
A magic tool Abon created otherwise known as the Tempest
If Arachnophobia get their hands on that
Yes, it would be bad news for the Academy indeed
My guess is that they've got all their top people working to acquire Brew
Stein, I don't think I need to tell you how serious this problem is
We can't waste any time
Speed up the students' dual arts class as much as you can
Resonance, Link
Play the melody of the souls?
There's another presence within Tsubaki
I have to understand the enchanted sword
You must try to grasp it, Black Star
You can sense me, but there is someone else here as well
Another wavelength for my family
Can you feel the weight he carries?
The tears of all the souls he's taken?
He's a part of me now, Black Star
He's always here, always with us
He's waiting for you
It is time for you to join us on the path we walk together
Why do you desire such great power?
I need it to surpass God
Is that so?
You would surpass God
And yet you look like a demon
Black Star
Are you okay?
Yeah, it's nothing
Found you!
The professor's looking for you
Everybody's going to practice resonating souls as a teen
Okay
You're still doing your special training?
Your body's going to start falling apart on you
If you don't take it easy
If I spend all my time worrying about my health
I won't get anything done
Now let's get going
We'll be late!
We're the ones who came to get you, remember?
Why is Black Star so determined to rush it like this?
It's okay professor, I brought everyone
You're late
What were you doing anyway?
Extra training?
Unlike you guys, I'm interested in expanding my education
So the enchanted sword's working well for you now
No sweat, I'm practically a god after all
Nothing's impossible for a big guy like me
Now why don't you turn all that confidence of yours to this lesson?
No problem
Okay
Now that I've got you all here, we can get started
There's something I need to tell you
As you know, we've been working on a new technique
Over the last week, I've been trying to get the seven of you to resonate your souls as a team
You have yet to succeed even once
Unless you try harder, you'll continue to fall further behind the other teams
Why am I pushing you?
Because arachnophobia has begun to move again
We believe a battle between them and us will happen soon
Given how little time we have remaining
I can't afford to slow this lesson down for any one team
So I'm afraid we're going to have to do this the hard way
Any team who still cannot resonate souls by the end of today
Will be dropped from my class
Got it?
I've seen this done loads of times
I can pull this off
Liz, Patty, I won't tolerate any slacking
Let's see your best work today
Alright, begin
This is important, so do it right, Blackstar
I always do, don't I?
Ready?
Yeah
Kid
Maka
OK, we're connected
So far, so good
Blackstar
Another failure
No resting again
Great
It's still not working
The reason they keep failing is obvious
Blackstar's wavelength is trying to take over
It won't accept Maka's lead and mesh with the others
But he may not be the only problem they have
I told you to do it right
I am, Maka
You never think of anyone but yourself, Blackstar
Try working with everybody else this time
Why bother?
Who would want to work with an idiot like you anyway?
Can't you see you're the weak link here?
Say that again, you punk
Guys, stop it
Let's go ahead and take a break
Maybe talking things through will help you clear your minds a little bit
There's no point in talking to a fool
This doesn't make sense
The madness shouldn't be progressing this quickly
Professor
What is it?
Unless something changes we aren't going to get any better
I don't want to be forced out of your class because of somebody else's mistakes
Please drop Blackstar from my resonance team
Is that what you came here to say?
The one who's failing the team is you
Now get out of my sight
How can you say that?
Blackstar is the one who's holding us up
It's not me
He's always so infuriatingly cocky
Let me get something straight
What you're asking is that Blackstar hold himself back
Is that correct?
Don't you see that's counterproductive?
Who do you think is the most powerful attacker on your team?
Why is everything all about Blackstar?
You seem to have misunderstood serial soul resonance somewhere along the line
You need to consider it on a more fundamental level
If you can't do this, you will leave my class
I'll do it
Oh?
I'm going to stay in your class, professor
I wish I could say the same
But things are changing
How much longer will I be able to teach properly?
Where did Maka run off to?We've got work to do
Maka
You went and whined about me to the professor?
Looks like I'm not the only one who's selfish, huh?
You!
I guess that's about all we have in common, though
I'm not some little weakling like you
Cut it out, you two
This is getting us no-
Let them handle it
Fine
You satisfied yet?
It doesn't matter to me if it is you, Maka
If you take this one step further, I'll consider it an official fight
I'll throw nothing back
I will crush you
You bastard!
I guess things aren't going well
Sorry, I deserve that
Will you help me?
Yep
Yes
Hey Maka
Can I sit?
Don't you get tired of it, Tsubaki?
Having your life ruled by Blackstar's whims?
Tell me
What do you think about Blackstar?
You can be honest
He drives me nuts
I've never told anyone before, but Blackstar actually studies for every test he takes
I doubt he'll ever admit to it though
What?
Seriously?
No way!
But then why does he always get zeros?
I wonder too
That takes talent
Studying and getting a zero sounds harder than getting a perfect score
You don't even completely understand him and you're his partner
When you think about that, how could I have any hope of matching his sole wavelength?
I don't know
You two have always gotten along pretty well
Besides, it's not such a bad thing if friends don't completely understand each other, is it?
You're two different people
So of course there'll be bits about each other that you don't get
That doesn't make your friendship any less real
And don't you think that friendship is enough of a foundation?
You seem to have misunderstood serial soul resonance somewhere along the line
You need to consider it on a more fundamental level
I do
That's it
I've been so worried about my own feelings that I forgot about what's really important
I'm ready to go back
Come on Tsubaki, hurry!
Hurry!
What happened?
You were so eager a second ago
I know, but what am I supposed to say when I get back?
I'm sure this isn't going to be the last time the two of you fight, so I wouldn't sweat it too much
So what?Did you come here to laugh at me?
No time now, we can laugh when we pass this damn test
Everyone's waiting
You know, honestly
I know that I don't
Always say the nicest things about Black Star
But the truth is, I'm often jealous of him
I wish that I could be as strong as he is somehow
That's all
I will die
Sorry, I was holding us back
Alright!
Let's get this party started!
What?Are you just gonna stand there, Maka?
Right
Okay, let's do this!
From here on out, we're entrusting our lives to each other.
We have to do our best to fulfill that trust.
I can feel them now. Both of their soul wavelengths. They're so powerful!
Hey, soul. You can hear it, can't you? Their soul wavelengths moving rhythmically together. Almost sounds like a song.
Let me help you.
Play the piano. Add your soul song to theirs. Then resonance will be easy.
You're a greedy demon, aren't you?
I think it's time for you to shut up.
I'm doing just fine on my own now.
I don't need to force myself to understand them.
I just need to accept who they are.
And believe.
People who are alike couldn't make this harmony.
The secret lies in our differences.
It's still a rough attempt, but you all pass.
This team's leader is...
Maka.
Well, we finally settled that problem.
It's so awesome! You guys passed!
I knew everything would work out.
It was looking a little rough when Maka started crying.
Women are more sensitive than men, Blackstar.
Yelling, not crying, thank you.
Why would I cry? Do I look like a baby?
But there's one other thing, Blackstar.
I think that you should hit me.
But... but why, Maka?
I hit you earlier. This'll be payback.
Right! You cannot be serious, Blackstar.
You cannot be serious, Blackstar.
But... but why, Maka?
I hit you earlier. This'll be payback.
Right!
You cannot be serious, Blackstar.
I'm not going to hold back.
Good! It wouldn't mean anything if you did.
Come on. Or are you afraid to hit a girl?
Do you realize who you're talking to?
No...
I'm not going to hold back!
I'm not gonna hold back!
It's good. It wouldn't be anything if you did.
Come on. Are you afraid if you hit a girl?
Do you realize who you're talking to?!
I hope you're ready through this.
Come on now, you could have held back a little.
Aw, dude, that was totally uncool.
Oh, ow!
All right, everyone. Listen carefully.
The demon tool Brew is Lady Arachne's.
The DWMA will not have it.
We can undoubtedly expect the enemy to attack in force, armed with death signs.
However, Brew will not make things easy for them.
Of that we can be sure.
Well, it's about time. All this waiting has nearly driven me crazy.
Hear me, everyone. This is war!
Without a hat, here it is.
Thank you.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, the battle for brew, Clash, the DWMA versus arachnophobia, watch it or I'll take your soul.